Kheel Center Collection of Oral Histories 6058 OH
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kheel Center Collection of Oral Histories
1965-1975
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kheel Center
6058 OH
27.44 cubic feet
27.4 linear ft.
Oral histories.
This collection is made up of oral history interviews from the NLRB (National Labor Relations Board), UTU (United Transportation Union), and others.
5797422
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 05, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, January 15, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Collective bargaining; Avrutis, William J.; Barghausen, Meta P.; Bokat, George; Bott, George; Boyls, Fannie M.; Brickman, Harry; Ching, Cyrus S.; Ching, Mildred; Cohen, Wallace M.; Consedine, William R.; Cushman, Bernard; Emerson, Thomas I.; Fields, Odgen W.; Frankfurter, Estelle S.; Fuchs, Herbert, 1918-; Garrison, Lloyd K.(Lloyd Kirkham), 1897- 1991; Glaser, Herbert R.; Golden, Ben; Gross, Ernest A.; Handler, Milton, 1903-1998.; Herzog, Paul M., 1906-1986; Hunt, A. Bruce; Keyserling, Leon H.(Leon Hirsch), 1908-1987.; Klaus, Ida; Kleiler, Frank M.; Levy, Philip; Lichtenstein, Howard; Madden, J. Warren; Mallet-Prevost, Marcel; Maslow, Will; Murdock, Ray R.; Pratt, George O.; Pressman, Lee, 1906-1969.; Robb, Roger; Silverberg, Louis; Smith, Edwin S.; Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives; Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives --Archives; State University College at Cortland; United States. National Labor Relations Board
5797422
- Ben Davidson (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  interview #1002
- Morris Schappes - March 9, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  interview # 1002a
- George Counts - March 23, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  interview #1002b
- Sidney Hook (Box 1, Folder 4)
  interview #1002c
- Cyrus S. Ching (Sept. 29, 1965) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  interview #1000; #1
- Cyrus S. Ching (Box 1, Folder 6)
  interview #1000; #2-#3
- Cyrus S. Ching (Box 1, Folder 7)
  interview #1000; #4-#5
- Cyrus S. Ching (Nov. 17, 1965, Dec. 1, 1965) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  interview #1000; #7-#8
- Cyrus S. Ching - (Dec. 6, 1965, Jan. 12, 1966) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  interview #1000; #9-#10
- Cyrus S. Ching - (April 28, 1966, June 22, 1966) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  interview #1000; #11-#12
- Cyrus S. Ching - (July 14, 1966, Sept. 15, 1966) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  interview #1000; #13
- Cyrus Ching - (9/12/1966, 9/21/1966) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  interview #1000; #14-#15
- Cyrus Ching - (October 25, 1966, November 2, 1966) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  interview #1000; #16-#17
- Cyrus S. Ching - (Nov. 22, 1966, Dec. 13, 1967) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  interview #1000; #18-#19
- Mrs. Cyrus Ching - (March 30, 1970) (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Herbert R. Glaser - (March 18, 1969) (Box 1, Folder 16)
  interview #1021
- Owsley Vose - (March 14, 1969) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  interview #1024
- Lee Pressman - (May 2, 1969) (Box 1, Folder 18)
  interview #1023
- E.S. Smith (Box 1, Folder 19)
  interview #1004
- E.S. Smith - (Dec. 27, 1968) (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Judge Joseph Warren Madden (Oct. 29, 1968) (Box 1, Folder 21)
  interview #1005
- Judge Madden - #2 - (Oct. 29, Oct. 31, 1968) (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Judge Madden - #3 - (Oct. 31, 1968) (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Nathan Witt (Feb. 19, 1969) (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Nathan Witt - (Feb. 18, 1969) (Box 1, Folder 25)
  interview #1007
- Herbert Fuchs - (March 18, 1969) (Box 1, Folder 26)
  interview #1008
- D. Saposs, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  tape #2 (July 24, 1968) -- interview #1001
- David Saposs, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  tape #1 - (July 22, 1968) --- interview #1001
- Charles Fahy - (July 23, 1968) (Box 1, Folder 29)
  interview #1003
- C. Fahy - Tape #2 (July 24, 1968) (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Wallace B. Cohen (March 21, 1969) (Box 1, Folder 31)
  interview #1010
- Bernard Cushman, Leon Keyserling (March 19, 1969) (Box 1, Folder 32)
  interview #1012
- Howard Lichtenstein (May 19, 1969) (Box 1, Folder 33)
  interview #1013
- Marcel Mallet-Prevest, Harry Brickman (March 17, 18, 1969) (Box 1, Folder 34)
  interview #1014
- Benedict Wolf (May 19, 1969) (Box 1, Folder 35)
  interview #1015
- Fannie Boyle, Geo. Bott - (1969) (Box 1, Folder 36)
  interview #1017
- William R. Consedine (March 18, 1969) (Box 1, Folder 37)
  interview #1019
- Ernest A. Gross (March 24, 1970) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  interview #1026
- Philip Levy (March 15, 1969) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  interview #1027
- Philip Levy (part II) - (March 21, 1969) (Box 2, Folder 3)
- George O. Pratt (March 18, 1970) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  interview #1028
- George O. Pratt (March 18, 1970) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  tape #2 - interview #1028
- A. Norman Somens (March 20, 1969) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  interview #1029
- John F. Collins (3/25/1970) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  interview #1030
- C.V. Grady (4/2/1970) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  interview #1031
- John J. Johnson (4/3/1970) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  interview #1032
- N.A. Rogers (3/24/1970) (Box 2, Folder 10)
  interview #1033
- David Wykle (Feb. 3, 1970) (Box 2, Folder 11)
  interview #1034
- Catherwood (3/6/1969) (Box 2, Folder 12)
  interview #1035
- Catherwood (March 22, 1969) (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Charles R. Bethage (4/29/1970) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  interview #1036
- William R. Donovan (April 30, 1970) (Box 2, Folder 15)
  interview #1037
- Jacob J. Kaufman (June 15, 1970) (Box 2, Folder 16)
  interview #1038
- William R. Welch (4/3/1970) (Box 2, Folder 17)
  interview #1039
- Lloyd K. Garrison (December 22, 1969) (Box 2, Folder 18)
  interview #1040
- Milton Handler (April 15, 1970) (Box 2, Folder 19)
  interview #1041
- Will Maslow (March 20, 1970) (Box 2, Folder 20)
  interview #1042
- Donald J. Crabtree, Sr. (6/22/1970) (Box 2, Folder 21)
  interview #1044
- Sidney Rosen (Box 2, Folder 22)
  interview #1045
- Michael W. Herr (6/25/1970) (Box 2, Folder 23)
  interview #1046
- R.J. O'Connor (6/26/1970) (Box 2, Folder 24)
  interview #1047
- Gerald W. Rogers (7/2/1970) (Box 2, Folder 25)
  interview #1048
- J. Slindden (Box 2, Folder 26)
  interview #1049
- George A. Stueben (Box 2, Folder 27)
  interview #1050
- James A. Schultz (July 15, 1970) (Box 2, Folder 28)
  interview #1052
- Gerhard VanArkel (Sept. 4, 1970) (Box 2, Folder 29)
  interview #1053
- Ida Klaus (Feb. 27, 1969) (Box 2, Folder 30)
  interview #1054 (1)
- Ida Klaus (4/16/1970) (Box 2, Folder 31)
  interview #1043 (2)
- Raymond Murdock (Box 2, Folder 32)
  interview #1055
- Parnell M. Aimome (8/3/1970) (Box 2, Folder 33)
  interview #1056
- Charles N. Benner (Aug. 19, 1970) (Box 2, Folder 34)
  interview #1057
- Willard W. Carson (Box 2, Folder 35)
  interview #1058
- Louis Broten, William Carson (Box 2, Folder 36)
  interview #1058 (2)
- Louis J. Broten (7/29/1969) (Box 2, Folder 37)
  interview #1058a
- W.W. Carson (Jan. 22, 1970) (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Willard W. Carson (Aug. 17, 1970) (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Al H Chesser (July 17, 1970) (Box 2, Folder 40)
  interview #1059
- Thomas J. Duggan (July 25, 1970) (Box 2, Folder 41)
  interview #1060)
- Robert O. Knupp (8/5/1970) (Box 2, Folder 42)
  interview #1061
- Roy H. Koepke (Aug. 21, 1970) (Box 2, Folder 43)
  interview #1062
- Lawrence J. Kroenert (8/7/1970) (Box 2, Folder 44)
  interview #1063
- Groat (Box 2, Folder 45)
  interview #1051
- Gerald R. Maloney (Aug. 21, 1970) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  interview #1064
- John J. Maurer (Aug. 18, 1970) (Box 3, Folder 2)
  interview #1065
- Thomas F. Purnell (7/30/1970) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  interview #1067
- Roger Robb (Mar. 3, 1969) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  interview #1068
- Joseph R. Coyne (6/24/1970) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  interview #1069
- M.W. Hampton (Nov. 2, 1970) (Box 3, Folder 6)
  interview #1070
- M.W. Hampton (Jan. 21, 1970) (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Donald Beattie (9/29/1970) (Box 3, Folder 8)
  interview #1971
- Francis B. Boardman (11/12/1970) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  interview #1072
- F.B. Boardman (4/9) (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Louis E. Chester (Nov. 2, 1970) (Box 3, Folder 11)
  interview #1073
- Thomas R. Moran (4/2/1970) (Box 3, Folder 12)
  interview #1074
- Leo M. Riley (4/3/1970) (Box 3, Folder 13)
  interview #1075
- Neil P. Speirs (July 21, 22, 1970) (Box 3, Folder 14)
  interview #1076
- Paul C. Weixlmann (10/26/1970) (Box 3, Folder 15)
  interview #1077
- Los Angeles Railway Labor Council Special Meeting (12/17/1970) (Box 3, Folder 16)
  interview #1078
- Los Angeles Railway Labor council Special Meeting (12/17/1970) (Box 3, Folder 17)
  interview #1078 [dupl.]
- Louis E. Chester (May 7, 1969) (Box 3, Folder 18)
  interview #1079
- Gerald C. Chisholm (Nov. 6, 1970) (Box 3, Folder 19)
  interview #1083
- John R. Burge (12/15/1970) (Box 3, Folder 20)
  interview #1084
- Luis Gonzalez (12/8/1970) (Box 3, Folder 21)
  interview #1085
- Neil G. Jenkins (Mar. 2, 1971) (Box 3, Folder 22)
  interview #1086
- James E. Howe (12/10/1970) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  interview #1087
- Lewis E. Silverberg (Mar. 6, 1970) (Box 3, Folder 24)
  interview #1088
- Ruth Weyand (Mar. 7, 1970) (Box 3, Folder 25)
  interview #1089
- Marvin F. Lofton (12/13/1970) (Box 3, Folder 26)
  interview #1090
- Kenneth R. Moore (12/18/1970) (Box 3, Folder 27)
  interview #1091
- Cue O. White (12/18/1970) (Box 3, Folder 28)
  interview #1092
- Thomas I. Emerson (March 9, 1970) (Box 3, Folder 29)
  interview #1093
- Estelle Frankfurter (Feb. 4, 1970) (Box 3, Folder 30)
  interview #1094
- Estelle Frankfurter (Jan. 21, 1970) (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Frank M. Kleiler (Feb. 23, 1971) (Box 3, Folder 32)
  interview #1095
- Fran Merman - Sid Rosen (11/9, 11/10/1970) (Box 3, Folder 33)
  interview #1096
- James T. Camp (Feb. 27, 1971) (Box 3, Folder 34)
  interview #1097
- Ray W. Guy (12/9/1970) (Box 3, Folder 35)
  interview #1098
- Lucius C. Hamilton (Mar. 2, 1971) (Box 3, Folder 36)
  interview #1099
- A.M. Lampley (July 17, 1970) (Box 3, Folder 37)
  interview #1100
- C.F. Lane (May 28, 1970) (Box 3, Folder 38)
  interview #1101
- Clyde F. Lane (June 15, 1971) (Box 3, Folder 39)
- J.W. McGinness (Aug. 18, 1970) (Box 3, Folder 40)
  interview #1102
- A. Miller (Nov. 5, 1970) (Box 3, Folder 41)
  interview #1103
- Don Adair Miller (April 1, 1971) (Box 3, Folder 42)
- John L. Rabbitt (April 4, 1970) (Box 3, Folder 43)
  interview #1105
- Vincent A. Tobia (4/28/1970) (Box 3, Folder 44)
  interview #1106
- J. Frank Young (12/14/1970) (Box 3, Folder 45)
  interview #1107
- H.E. Gilbert, L.E. Chester (May 27, 1970) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  interview #1108
- H.E. Gilbert (6/18/1971) (Box 4, Folder 2)
- H.E. Gilbert (June 18, 1971) (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Michael R. Alamprese (11/5/1970) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  interview #1109
- Walter H. Canty (Aug. 19, 1970) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  interview #1110
- Charlie J. Chamberlain (Nov. 3, 1970) (Box 4, Folder 6)
  interview #1111
- Howard D. Fleenor (12/14/1970) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  interview #1112
- Q.C. Gabriel (Nov. 3, 1970) (Box 4, Folder 8)
  interview #1113
- Emory Harris (Aug. 16, 1971) (Box 4, Folder 9)
  interview #1114
- A.E. Lyons (Nov. 5, 1970) (Box 4, Folder 10)
  interview #1115
- John L. Pickett (Aug. 17, 1971) (Box 4, Folder 11)
  interview #1116
- L. Shattuck (May 27, 1970) (Box 4, Folder 12)
  interview #1117
- Charles W. Zies (12/17/1970) (Box 4, Folder 13)
  interview #1118
- G. Bokat (March 1969) (Box 4, Folder 14)
  interview #1119
- George P. Blazin (Aug. 19, 1971) (Box 4, Folder 15)
  interview #1120
- John Blount (Aug. 18, 1971) (Box 4, Folder 16)
  interview #1121
- Walter H. Callies (Aug. 20, 1970) (Box 4, Folder 17)
  interview #1122
- Norman R. Dommermath (Mar. 30, 1971) (Box 4, Folder 18)
  interview #1123
- M.E. Eastman (March 31, 1971) (Box 4, Folder 19)
  interview #1124
- Robert W. Godwin (10/27/1970) (Box 4, Folder 20)
  interview #1125
- Robert W. Groah (11/4/1970) (Box 4, Folder 21)
  interview #1126
- Richard W. Hare (10/15/1970) (Box 4, Folder 22)
  interview #1127
- Joseph F. Hoffman (12/17/1970) (Box 4, Folder 23)
  interview #1128
- Charles Luna (October 11, 1971) (Box 4, Folder 24)
  interview #1129
- George R. Perkins (12/8/1970) (Box 4, Folder 25)
  interview #1130
- M.F. Radrizzi (April 2, 1971) (Box 4, Folder 26)
  interview #1131
- W.D. Schwieger (8/17/1970) (Box 4, Folder 27)
  interview #1132
- John F. Spanfelner (11/11/1970) (Box 4, Folder 28)
  interview #1133
- M.S. Stuckey (8/6/1970) (Box 4, Folder 29)
  interview #1134
- Jesse L. Summers, Jr. (Mar. 1, 1971) (Box 4, Folder 30)
  interview #1135
- Donald J. Swain (12/9/1970) (Box 4, Folder 31)
  interview #1136
- James B. Vanders (Feb. 28, 1971) (Box 4, Folder 32)
  interview #1137
- Calvin F. Watson (8/17/1970) (Box 4, Folder 33)
  interview #1138
- Ben L. Wedding (8/4/1970) (Box 4, Folder 34)
  interview #1139
- Mrs. Beatrice M. Burgoon (June 17, 1971) (Box 4, Folder 35)
  interview #1140
- Ed Heisler (11/6/1970) (Box 4, Folder 36)
  interview #1141
- E.T. Heisler (July 24, 1970) (Box 4, Folder 37)
- J. Pryor (Nov. 10, 1970) (Box 4, Folder 38)
  interview #1142
- Thomas A. Tracy (June 17, 1971) (Box 4, Folder 39)
  interview #1143
- Paul Herzog (July 16, 1975) (Box 4, Folder 40)
  interview #1145a
- Paul Herzog (July 16, 1975) (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Paul Herzog (Jan. 6, 1972) (Box 4, Folder 42)
  interview #1145
- Paul Herzog (July 16, 1975) (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Paul Herzog (Box 4, Folder 44)
  interview #1145 -- pt. 1-4 (4 cassettes)
- References (Box 5, Folder 1)
- UTU Misc. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- UTU - Personnel Appointments (Box 5, Folder 3)
- UTU - Business Statements (Box 5, Folder 4)
- UTU - Proposals (Memorandum of Understanding) (Box 5, Folder 5)
- UTU - Travel (Box 5, Folder 6)
- UTU - Oral History (Box 5, Folder 7)
- B (Box 5, Folder 8)
- C (Box 5, Folder 9)
- D (Box 5, Folder 10)
- UTU = Oral History "E" (Box 5, Folder 11)
- F (Box 5, Folder 12)
- G (Box 5, Folder 13)
- H (Box 5, Folder 14)
- UTU - Oral History J (Box 5, Folder 15)
- K (Box 5, Folder 16)
- OH L (Box 5, Folder 17)
- UTU - Oral History - M (Box 5, Folder 18)
- N-O (Box 5, Folder 19)
- P (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Q-R (Box 5, Folder 21)
- OH - S (Box 5, Folder 22)
- T (Box 5, Folder 23)
- U-Z (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Oral History - Misc. (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Bulletin of Cornell Program in Oral History (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Oral History Listings (Box 5, Folder 27)
- OH# 1002-1003 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Oral History - UTU - Listing (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Davidson, Ben OH#1002 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  RESTRICTED
- Schappes, Mom's OH #1002a (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Saposs, David J. OH #1001 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Ching, Cyrus S. OH #1000 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Ching, Cyrus OH#1000 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Ching, Cyrus OH #1000 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Ching, Cyrus OH #1000 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Ching, Cyrus OH #1000 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Ching, Cyrus OH #1000 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Ching, Cyrus OH #1000 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Ching, Cyrus OH #1000 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Ching, Mildred V. OH 1000a (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Fahy, Charles OH 1003 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Hook, Sydney OH 1002c (Box 6, Folder 2)
- OH 1004-1006 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Smith, Edwin S. OH 1004 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Madden, J. Warren OH 1005 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Madden, J. Warren OH 1005 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Smith, Howard OH 1006 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- OH 1008-1015 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Witt, Nathan OH 1007 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Avrutis, William J. OH 1008 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Barghausen, Meta P. OH 1009 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Cohen, Wallace M. OH 1010 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Fuchs, Herbert OH 1011 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Keyserling, Leon H. OH 1012 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Lichtenstein, Howard OH 1013 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Mallet-Prevost, Marcel OH 1014 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Wolf, Benedict OH 1015 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Bott, George J. OH 1016 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Boyls, Fannie OH 1017 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Brickman, Harry OH 1018 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- OH 1016-1024 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Glaser, Herbert R. OH 1021 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Hunt, A. Bruce OH 1022 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Consedine, William R. OH 1019 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Cushman, Bernard OH 1020 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Counts, George S. OH 1002b (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Pressman, Lee OH 1023 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Vose, Owsley OH 1024 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- OH 1025-1029 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Fields, Ogden W. OH 1025 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Gross, Ernest A. OH 1026 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- OH 1030-1034 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Levy, Philip OH 1027 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Pratt, George O. OH 1028 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Somers, A. Norman OH 1029 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Collins, John F. OH 1030 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Grady, Christopher V. OH 1031 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Johnson, John J. OH 1032 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Rogers, Norman J. OH 1033 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Wykle, David J. OH 1034 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- OH 1035 - OH 1039 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Catherwood, Martin P. OH 1035 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Bethge, Charles R. OH 1036 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Donovan, William R. OH 1037 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Kaupman, Jacab J. OH 1038 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Welch, William R. OH 1039 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Garrison, Lloyd K. OH 1040 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Handler, Milton OH 1041 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- OH 1040 - 1050 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Maslow, Will OH 1042 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Surrey, Stanley S. OH 1043 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Crabtree, Donald J. O. OH 1044 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Field, Gale R. OH 1045 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Herr, Michael W. OH 1046 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- O'Connor, Robert J. OH 1047 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Rogers, Gerald W. OH 1048 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Sludden, Charles J. OH 1049 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Steubner, George A. OH 1050 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- OH 1052-1053 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Groat, Wm. B. (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Schultz, James A. OH 1052 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Van Arkel, Gerhard P. OH 1053 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Klaus, Ida OH 1054 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- OH 1054 -1067 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Murdock, Ray R. OH 1055 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Aimone, Parnell M. OH 1056 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Benner, Charles N. OH 1057 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Carson, Willard W. OH 1058 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Broten, Louis J. OH 1058a (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Cheser, Al H. OH 1059, L h. Oh 1059 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Duggan, Thomas J. OH 1060 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Knupp, Robert O. OH 1061 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Koepke, Roy H. OH 1062 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Kroenert, Lawrence J. OH 1063 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Maloney, Gerald R. OH 1064 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Maurer, John J. OH 1065 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Meehan, Bernard R. OH 1066 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Purnell, Thomas F. OH 1067 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- OH 1068-1078 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Robb, Roger OH 1068 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Coyne, Joseph R. OH 1069 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Hampton, M.W. OH 1070 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Beattie, Donald S. OH 1071 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Boardman, Francis B. OH 1072 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Chester, Louis E. OH 1073 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Moran, Thomas R. OH 1074 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Riley, Leo M. OH 1075 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Spiers, Neil P. OH 1076 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Weixlman, Paul C. OH 1077 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Los Angeles Railway Labor Council Meeting OH 1078 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  No transcript rec'd 3/1971
- OH 1079-1095 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Chester, Louis E. OH 1079 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Canty, Walter H. OH 1080 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Peters, Homer E. OH 1082 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Chrisholm, Louis OH 1083 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Burge, John R. OH 1084 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Gonzalez, Luis OH 1085 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Bennett, Paul R. OH 1086 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Jenkins and Harden OH 1086 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Howe and Evans OH 1087 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Silverberg, L.G. OH 1088 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Weyand, Ruth OH 1089 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Lofton, M.F. OH 1090 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Moore, R.R. OH 1091 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- White, C.O. OH 1092 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Emerson, T. I. OH 1093 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Frankfurter, E. OH 1094 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Kleiler, Frank M. OH 1095 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Herman, Fran (Box 10, Folder 3)
  Interview w/ Sid Rosen - UTU Project (no transcript)
- OH 1097-1108 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Camp, James T. OH 1097 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Guy, Ray W. OH 1098 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Hamilton, Lucius C. (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Lamplay, A. M. OH 1100 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Lane, Clyde F. OH 1101 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- McGinness, John W. OH 1102 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Miller, Don A. OH 1103 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Pound, Ernest P. OH 1104 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Rabbitt, John L. OH 1105 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Tobia, Vincent A. OH 1106 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Young, J. Frank OH 1107 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Gilbert, Henry E. OH 1108 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- OH 1109-1118 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Alamprese, Michael R. OH 1109 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Canty, Walter H. OH 1110 [EMPTY] (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Chamberlain, Charles J. OH 1111 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Fleenor, Howard D. OH 1112 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Gabriel, Quinton C. OH 1113 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Harris, Emory OH 1114 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Lyon, Arlon E. OH 1115 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Pickett, John L. OH 1116 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Shattuck, Jess L. OH 1117 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Zies, Charles W. OH 1118 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Bokat, George OH 1119 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Blazin, George P. OH 1120 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Blunt, John H. OH 1121 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Callies, Walter H. OH 1122 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  ESTRICTED
- Dommermuth, Norman R. OH 1123 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Eastman, Merrill E., Jr. OH 1124 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Godwin, Robert W. OH 1125 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Groah, Robert W. OH 1126 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Hare, Richard W. OH 1127 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Hoffman, Joseph F. OH 1128 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Luna, Charles OH 1129 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Perkins, George R. OH 1130 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Radrizzi, Maurice F. OH 1131 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Schwieger, William D. OH 1132 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Spanfelner, John F. OH 1133 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Stuckey, M.S. OH 1134 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- OH 1119-1139 -- Comments, etc. (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Summers, Jesse L., Jr. OH 1135 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Swain, Donald J. OH 1136 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Vanders, James B. OH 1137 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Watson, Calvin F. OH 1138 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Wedding, Ben L. OH 1139 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Burgoon, Beatrice OH 1140 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Pryor, Harold J. OH 1142 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- OH 1140-1143 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Heisler, Edward T. OH 1141 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Heisler, Edward T. OH 1141 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Heisler, Edward T. OH 1141 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Tracy, Thomas A. OH 1143 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Herzog and MacKenzie Transcript OH 1145a (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Herzog, Paul M. OH 1145 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Golden, Ben OH 1146 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Margison, Richard L. (Box 12, Folder 8)
- OH 1145-1146 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Jones, Richard C. (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Swarr, Philip (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Reynolds, H. Kendall (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Brooks, Rozanne (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Brennan, Daniel J. (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Corey, William T. (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Palm, Delmar (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Leon, Donald (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Rzepka, Louis (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Miners for Democracy OH 1144, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  Philip Kugler
- Miners for Democracy OH 1144, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  Hobart Grills
- Miners of Democracy OH 1144, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  interviewer - Philip Kugler
- Miners for Democracy OH 1144, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  Hatfert Rhea and Carl J. Breeding
- Miners for Democracy OH 1144, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  Robert Payne and Lucien Conn
- Miners for Democracy OH 1144, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  Jake Campbell
- Iushewitz, Morris (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Loomis (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Abelson, Paul (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Paddock (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Weaver and Hardin Interview (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Paddock (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Loomis, Daniel P. (copy) (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Paddock (Box 13, Folder 8)